PG 160, Floods and Hurricanes in Connecticut
Connecticut State Library
- Series 2. Hurricane of 1938, T001765
  - Oblique Views, Numerical listing
    - Connecticut Shore
      - New London (Box 12, Envelope 103)
      - New London (Box 12, Envelope 104)
      - New London. Hendel's Home Furishers; many rooftops ripped off (Box 12, Envelope 105)
      - New London. Smokestacks of ships sunk at dock (Box 12, Envelope 106)
      - New London. Envelope says "Bluff Point, Groton", But possibly New London docks? (Box 12, Envelope 107)
      - New London. Fort Trumbull (Box 12, Envelope 108)
      - Groton. Shennecossett Beach (Box 12, Envelope 109)
      - Groton. Griswold Hotel (Box 12, Envelope 110)
      - Groton. Bluff Point (Box 12, Envelope 111)
      - Groton. Trumbull Field (Box 12, Envelope 112)
      - Groton. Baker's Cove (Box 12, Envelope 113)
      - Groton. Noank (Box 12, Envelope 114)
    - Rhode Island Shore
      - Westerly R.I. Watch Hill, R.I. (Box 12, Envelope 115)
      - Westerly, R.I. Watch Hill, R.I. (Box 12, Envelope 116)
      - Westerly, R.I. Misquamicut Beach, R.I. (Box 12, Envelope 117)
      - Westerly, R.I. Misquamicut Beach, R.I. (Box 12, Envelope 118)
      - Westerly, R.I. Atlantic Beach, R.I. (Box 12, Envelope 119)
      - Westerly, R.I. Weekapaug Beach, R.I. (Box 12, Envelope 120)
      - Charlestown, R.I. Quonochontaug (Box 12, Envelope 121)
      - Charlestown, R.I. Quonochontaug, R.I. (Box 12, Envelope 122)
      - Charlestown, R.I. Quonochontaug, R.I. (Box 12, Envelope 123)
      - Charlestown, R.I. Charlestown Beach (Box 12, Envelope 124)
      - Green Hill, R.I. (Box 12, Envelope 125)
      - South Kingstown, R.I. Telephone poles on beach (Box 12, Envelope 126)
      - Matunuck, R.I. House in the water (Box 12, Envelope 127)
      - Galillee, R.I. (Box 12, Envelope 128)
      - Point Judith, R.I. (Box 12, Envelope 129)
      - Narragansett, R.I. Scarborough, R.I. Scarborough is mispelled on photo, says "Scarbarough" (Box 12, Envelope 130)
      - Narragansett, R.I. Dunes Clubs (Box 12, Envelope 131)
      - Narragansett, R.I. Lower Narragansett Bay (Box 12, Envelope 132)
  - Oblique View, Alphabetical Listing
    Same photographs as in numerical listing above, listed here alphabetically by town.
    - Ashford, CT (Envelope 38)
    - Atlantic Beach, RI (Envelope 119)
    - Baltic, CT (Envelope 46-48)
    - Branford, CT (Envelope 59-61)
    - Carpenters Beach, RI (Envelope 126)
    - Charlestown Beach, RI (Envelope 124)
    - Clinton, CT (Envelope 74-77)
    - Cromwell, CT (Envelope 27)
    - Eagleville, CT (Envelope 36)
    - East Hartford, CT (Envelope 18-23)
    - East Haven, CT (Envelope 54-58)
    - East Lyme, CT (Envelope 89-92)
    - Galillee, RI (Envelope 128)
    - Green Hill, RI (Envelope 125)
    - Groton, CT (Envelope 109-113)
    - Guildford, CT (Envelope 62)
    - Hartford and East Hartford, CT (Envelope 16-17)
    - Hartford, CT (Envelope 1-15)
    - Madison, CT (Envelope 63-73)
    - Matunuck, RI (Envelope 127)
    - Miscquamicut, RI (Envelope 117-118)
    - Narragansett (Dunes Club), RI (Envelope 131)
    - Narragansett Bay, RI (Envelope 132)
    - New London, CT (Envelope 97-108)
    - Niantic, CT (Envelope 93-95)
    - Noank, CT (Envelope 114)
    - Norwich, CT (Envelope 52-53)
    - Occum, CT (Envelope 49-50)
    - Old Lyme, CT (Envelope 84-88)
    - Point Judicth, RI (Envelope 129)
    - Putnam, CT (Envelope 28)
    - Quonochontaug, RI (Envelope 121-123)
    - Saybrook, CT (Envelope 82-83)
    - Scarbarough, RI (Envelope 130)
    - Scotland, CT (Envelope 45)
    - South Windham, CT (Envelope 44)
    - Stafford Springs, CT (Envelope 29-32)
    - Taftville, CT (Envelope 51)
    - Versailles, CT (Envelope 49-50)
    - Watch Hill, RI (Envelope 115-116)
    - Waterford, CT (Envelope 96)
    - Weekapaug, RI (Envelope 120)
    - West Ashford, CT (Envelope 37)
    - Westbrook, CT (Envelope 78-81)
    - Wethersfield, CT (Envelope 24-26)
    - Willimantic, CT (Envelope 39-43)
    - Willington, CT (Envelope 33-35)
  - Myron Johnson Collection, 1938; T001765
    - Man standing in front of truck (Box 21, Envelope 1)
    - Truck with barrels in it (Box 21, Envelope 2)
    - Truck parked outside of house with men gathered (Box 21, Envelope 3)
    - Distance shot of truck being loaded (Box 21, Envelope 4)
    - Picture of flat bed truck (Box 21, Envelope 5)
    - Flooded trees (Box 21, Envelope 6)
  - Mildred Davieau Collection, 1938; T001765
    - Colt's Park near Armsmear (Box 21, Envelope 19)
- Series 3. Flood of 1955
  - Towns, T001765
    - Putnam. Clothing depot, dresses for the disaster victims (Box 13, Envelope 1)
    - Putnam. Supply of groceries for the disaster victims (Box 13, Envelope 2)
    - Putnam. Unloading truck (Box 13, Envelope 3)
    - Putnam (Box 13, Envelope 4)
    - Putnam. Rushing flood, car on right (Box 13, Envelope 5)
    - Putnam. Quinnebaug River (Box 13, Envelope 6)
    - Putnam (Box 13, Envelope 7)
    - Putnam. Barber shop (Box 13, Envelope 8)
    - Putnam. House under water (Box 13, Envelope 9)
    - Putnam. Destroyed building (Box 13, Envelope 10)
    - Putnam. Houses under water (Box 13, Envelope 11)
    - Putnam. Collapsed bridge, Arch Street Bridge (Box 13, Envelope 12)
    - Putnam. Fallen Arch Street Bridge (Box 13, Envelope 13)
    - Putnam. Men observing flooding (Box 13, Envelope 14)
    - Putnam. Man working on broken pipe line (Box 13, Envelope 15)
    - Putnam. Damaged building (Box 13, Envelope 16)
    - Putnam. Crane (Box 13, Envelope 17)
    - Putnam. Chapel Street from Truesdell Street (Box 13, Envelope 18)
    - Putnam. Chapel Street from Green Street (Box 13, Envelope 19)
    - Putnam. Water Street from Bridge Street (Box 13, Envelope 20)
    - Putnam. Railroad tracks (Box 13, Envelope 21)
    - Putnam. Washout around Providence Street Bridge abutment (Box 13, Envelope 22)
    - Putnam. French River from Bolles Street (Box 13, Envelope 23)
    - Putnam. Damaged department store (Box 13, Envelope 24)
    - Torrington. High water mark at 19 East Main Street at Center Square (Box 13, Envelope 25)
    - Torrington. Overhead view of Torrington (Box 13, Envelope 26)
    - Torrington. Naugatuck River Center Square (Box 13, Envelope 27)
    - Torrington. Man in front of City Cab Taxi (Box 13, Envelope 28)
    - Torrington. Church Street Bridge (Box 13, Envelope 29)
    - Torrington. Main and East Main Street (Box 13, Envelope 30)
    - Torrington. West from church Street Bridge (Box 13, Envelope 31)
    - Torrington. Naugatuck River at Center Square (Box 13, Envelope 32)
    - Torrington. Naugatuck River at Center Square (Box 13, Envelope 33)
    - Torrington. Lumber against Prospect Street Bridge (Box 13, Envelope 34)
    - Torrington. Naugatuck River at Center Square (Box 13, Envelope 35)
    - Torrington. East from Prospect Street Bridge (Box 13, Envelope 36)
    - Torrington. East Main Street looking east (Box 13, Envelope 37)
    - Torrington. High water mark on church (Box 13, Envelope 38)
    - Torrington. East Main Street at Wall Street Bridge (Box 13, Envelope 39)
    - Torrington. Gas station on East Main Street (Box 13, Envelope 40)
    - Torrington. East Main Street from Main Street (Box 13, Envelope 41)
    - Torrington. East Main Street from Main Street (Box 13, Envelope 42)
    - Torrington. East from Church Street Bridge (Box 13, Envelope 43)
    - Torrington. Naugatuck River at Center Square (Box 13, Envelope 44)
    - Torrington. West Torrington, bridge and square (Box 13, Envelope 45)
    - Torrington, West Torrington bridge and square (Box 13, Envelope 46)
    - Torrington. High water mark on Church Street (Box 13, Envelope 47)
    - Torrington. West from Prospect Street bridge (Box 13, Envelope 48)
    - Torrington. East from Church Street Bridge (Box 13, Envelope 49)
    - Torrington. East Main Street looking east (Box 13, Envelope 50)
    - Torrington. West from Prospect Street bridge (Box 13, Envelope 51)
    - Winsted. House along Still River (Box 13, Envelope 52)
    - Winsted. Housing along Still River, high water mark on lawn (Box 13, Envelope 53)
    - Winsted. Replacing bridge over Still Bridge (Box 13, Envelope 54)
    - Torrington. American Brass Company (Box 13, Envelope 55)
    - Winsted. Main Street north from Bridge Street (Box 14, Envelope 1)
    - Winsted (Box 14, Envelope 2)
    - Winsted. Overview (Box 14, Envelope 3)
    - Winsted. Main Street north from Bridge Street (Box 14, Envelope 4)
    - Winsted. Main Street looking north (Box 14, Envelope 5)
    - Winsted. Madins Garage (Box 14, Envelope 6)
    - Winsted. Three soldiers (Box 14, Envelope 7)
    - Winsted. One soldier looking at building (Box 14, Envelope 8)
    - Winsted. Road to sewage treatment plant (Box 14, Envelope 9)
    - Winsted. Gauging at Highland Lake, West Spillway (Box 14, Envelope 10)
    - Winsted. Mad River Peak looking downstream from Case Street Bridge (Box 14, Envelope 11)
    - Winsted. Looking up the Mad River toward gas line crossing (Box 14, Envelope 12)
    - Winsted. Gas line crossing at flood peak (Box 14, Envelope 13)
    - Winsted. Sewage treatment plant at flood peak (Box 14, Envelope 14)
    - Winsted. Mad River dropping (Box 14, Envelope 15)
    - Norwalk. Main and Wall Street (Box 14, Envelope 16)
    - Norwalk. Wrecked boats and barges on Norwalk River (Box 14, Envelope 17)
    - Norwalk. Wall Street and Main (Box 14, Envelope 18)
    - Norwalk. Damage at Connecticut Light and Power Company (Box 14, Envelope 19)
    - Norwalk. Damage in vicinity of parking lot (Box 14, Envelope 20)
    - Norwalk. Damage along New Haven Railroad tracks (Box 14, Envelope 21)
    - Norwalk. Silvermine River washout near Route 7 (Box 14, Envelope 22)
    - Norwalk. Damaged building on Wall Street (Box 14, Envelope 23)
    - Norwalk. Damaged Broad Street Bridge (Box 14, Envelope 24)
    - Norwalk. Aerial view (Box 14, Envelope 25)
    - Norwalk. Aerial view (Box 14, Envelope 26)
    - Norwalk. Wall Street Bridge from downtown parking lot (Box 14, Envelope 27)
    - Norwalk. Damage on Cross Street (Box 14, Envelope 28)
    - Norwalk. Damaged building on Wall Street (Box 14, Envelope 29)
    - Norwalk. Wall Street damage (Box 14, Envelope 30)
    - Norwalk. Damaged building on Wall Street (Box 14, Envelope 31)
    - Norwalk. Damage in vicininty of parking lot, one women was killed here (Box 14, Envelope 32)
    - Norwalk. Main and Wall Street (Box 14, Envelope 33)
    - Norwalk (Box 14, Envelope 34)
    - Norwalk. Entrance to parking lot (Box 14, Envelope 35)
    - Norwalk. Near Wall Street Bridge (Box 14, Envelope 36)
    - Norwalk. Damage at New Haven RailRoad crossing (Box 14, Envelope 37)
    - Norwalk. Right side of Main and Wall Street (Box 14, Envelope 38)
    - Norwalk. Badly damaged Broad Street Bridge (Box 14, Envelope 39)
    - Norwalk. Damage at Connecticut Light and Power (Box 14, Envelope 40)
    - Norwalk. Damage along New Haven Railroad tracks (Box 14, Envelope 41)
    - Norwalk. Damage along Norwalk River taken from Wall Street Bridge (Box 14, Envelope 42)
    - Norwalk. Cross Street Bridge wreckage (Box 14, Envelope 43)
    - Norwalk. Damage at Cross Street Bridge (Box 14, Envelope 44)
    - Norwalk. Damage on Canaan Street past the Canaan Street Bridge (Box 14, Envelope 45)
    - Norwalk. Two families who lost their homes are registering with the Red Cross (Box 14, Envelope 46)
    - Norwalk. Damage in vincinity of parking lot (Box 14, Envelope 47)
    - Norwalk. Silvermine River and Merritt parkway washout (Box 14, Envelope 48)
    - Norwalk. Damaged barges near New Haven Railroad (Box 14, Envelope 49)
    - Norwalk. Cross Street Bridge Damage (Box 14, Envelope 50)
    - Norwalk. City Center (Box 14, Envelope 51)
    - Norwalk. Wall Street Bridge from downstream parking lot (Box 14, Envelope 52)
    - Naugatuck. Man working in hole (Box 14, Envelope 53)
    - Naugatuck. Picture from rescue helicopter (Box 14, Envelope 54)
    - Naugatuck. Picture taken from Sikorsky S-58 helicopter (Box 14, Envelope 55)
    - Naugatuck (Box 14, Envelope 56)
    - Naugatuck. Railroad tracks (Box 14, Envelope 57)
    - Naugatuck. Maple Street Bridge (Box 14, Envelope 58)
    - Naugatuck. Hotchkiss Street (Box 14, Envelope 59)
    - Naugatuck. Naugatuck Chemical Company (Box 14, Envelope 60)
    - Label detached from photograph (Box 14, Envelope 61)
    - Simsbury. Tarriffville Bridge below Simsbury looking upstream (Box 15, Envelope 1)
    - Simsbury. Tarriffvile road, from Simsbury Route 202 (Box 15, Envelope 2)
    - Simsbury. Below Simsbury looking downstream (Box 15, Envelope 3)
    - Simsbury. River at Drake Hill Road (Box 15, Envelope 4)
    - Simsbury. Ensign-Brickford Company (Box 15, Envelope 5)
    - Simsbury. Hop Brook Ensign-Brickford Company (Box 15, Envelope 6)
    - Simsbury. West branch Farmington River (Box 15, Envelope 7)
    - Simsbury. Farmington River Bridge (Box 15, Envelope 8)
    - Simsbury. Ensign-Bickford Company (Box 15, Envelope 9)
    - Simsbury. Hop Brook (Box 15, Envelope 10)
    - Simsbury. Ensign-Bickford Company (Box 15, Envelope 11)
    - Avon. House on its side (Box 15, Envelope 12)
    - Avon. Car in the woods; house on it's side (Box 15, Envelope 13)
    - East Granby. Spoonville Bridge (Box 15, Envelope 14)
    - East Granby. Craig Mill (Box 15, Envelope 15)
    - North Granby. Bridge over Mt. Brook (Box 15, Envelope 16)
    - East Granby. Junction Route 9 and Highway 187 street signs (Box 15, Envelope 17)
    - Granby. Salmon Brook (Box 15, Envelope 18)
    - East Granby. Farmington River (Box 15, Envelope 19)
    - East Granby. Sheldons Brook (Box 15, Envelope 20)
    - East Granby. Sheldons Brook (Box 15, Envelope 20)
    - Barkhamsted. Reservoir spillway (Box 15, Envelope 21)
    - Barkhamsted. Reservoir spillway (Box 15, Envelope 22)
    - Westfield. Route 202 (Box 15, Envelope 23)
    - Westfield, Mass. Westfield Motor Sales (Box 15, Envelope 24)
    - Unknown town. Two soliders on bridge (Box 15, Envelope 25)
    - New Hartford. Three soldiers (Box 15, Envelope 26)
    - Southbridge, Mass. Quinnebaug River (Box 15, Envelope 27)
    - Windsor Locks. Railroad tracks from overpass (Box 15, Envelope 28)
    - Windsor Locks. Connecticut River (Box 15, Envelope 29)
    - Unknown town. Salmon Brook (Box 15, Envelope 30)
    - Hartford. Men unloading truck (Box 15, Envelope 31)
    - Ansonia. Highway (Box 16, Envelope 1)
    - Ansonia. Bailey bridge knocked out (Box 16, Envelope 2)
    - Ansonia. Bridge Street looking upstream (Box 16, Envelope 3)
    - Ansonia. Flooded bridge (Box 16, Envelope 4)
    - Ansonia. Women giving clothing (Box 16, Envelope 5)
    - Ansonia. Maple Street (Box 16, Envelope 6)
    - Ansonia. Overhead view (Box 16, Envelope 7)
    - Beacon Falls. Pines bridge (Box 16, Envelope 8)
    - Danbury. Picture taken from National Guard plane (Box 16, Envelope 9)
    - Danbury. Flooded buildings (Box 16, Envelope 10)
    - Danbury. Crosby Street (Box 16, Envelope 11)
    - Danbury. Heyman Hardware Company (Box 16, Envelope 12)
    - Danbury. Broken telephone pole (Box 16, Envelope 13)
    - Danbury. Power lines (Box 16, Envelope 14)
    - Danbury. Drilling (Box 16, Envelope 15)
    - Norfolk. Blackberry River (Box 16, Envelope 16)
    - Union City. Curtis Street (Box 16, Envelope 17)
    - Waterbury. Bailey Bridge (Box 16, Envelope 18)
    - Waterbury. Bailey Bridge on upstream side (Box 16, Envelope 19)
    - Unknown town. Mayor of Hartford loading truck (Box 16, Envelope 20)
    - Hartford or Unionville. Men's social services department (Box 16, Envelope 21)
    - Possibly Farmington. Women rescued with help from army helicopter (Box 16, Envelope 22)
    - Unknown town. Collapsed bridge (Box 16, Envelope 23)
    - Canaan. Bridge damaged (Box 16, Envelope 24)
    - Unknown town. Damaged building and roads (Box 16, Envelope 25)
    - Unknown town. Spillway (Box 16, Envelope 26)
    - Unknown town. The Seymour Manufacturing Company and The Phospher Bronze Corporation (Box 16, Envelope 27)
    - Derby. Destroyed Railroad (Box 16, Envelope 28)
    - Darien. Overhead view of Train wreck (Box 16, Envelope 29)
    - Darien. Overhead view of train wreck (Box 16, Envelope 30)
    - Wilton. Overhead view of town (Box 16, Envelope 31)
    - Unknown town. Overhead view from army plane (Box 16, Envelope 32)
    - Unknown town. West branch Farmington River (Box 16, Envelope 33)
    - Unknown town (Box 16, Envelope 34)
    - Waterbury. The American Brass Company (Box 16, Envelope 35)
    - Unknown town. Railroad tracks (Box 16, Envelope 36)
    - Unknown town. Tobacco sheds (Box 16, Envelope 37)
    - Beacon Falls. Naugatuck River (Box 16, Envelope 38)
  - Black Friday, T001765
    - Naugatuck. Flooded down town, people on boat (Box 17, Envelope 1)
    - Naugatuck. Man in front of Connecticut Light and Power Company with his boat (Box 17, Envelope 2)
    - Naugatuck. Overhead Navy helicopter with man on a tether above flood waters. (Box 17, Envelope 3)
    - Naugatuck. Flooded buildings (Box 17, Envelope 4)
    - Naugatuck. Flooded water rising water (Box 17, Envelope 5)
    - Naugatuck. Mobile gas station (Box 17, Envelope 6)
    - Naugatuck. Mobil gas station (Box 17, Envelope 7)
    - Naugatuck (Box 17, Envelope 8)
    - Naugatuck. Downtown pile of wood (Box 17, Envelope 9)
    - Naugatuck. Downtown, pile of wood (Box 17, Envelope 10)
    - Naugatuck. Downtown, pile of wood (Box 17, Envelope 11)
    - Naugatuck. Dairy (Box 17, Envelope 12)
    - Naugatuck. Dairy (Box 17, Envelope 13)
    - Naugatuck. Overhead light post (Box 17, Envelope 14)
    - Naugatuck. Broken light post (Box 17, Envelope 15)
    - Naugatuck. Water rushing in Naugatuck Dairy (Box 17, Envelope 16)
    - Naugatuck. Water rushing into Naugatuck Dairy (Box 17, Envelope 17)
    - Naugatuck. Water rushing into Naugatuck Dairy (Box 17, Envelope 18)
    - Naugatuck. Helicopter flying over flood (Box 17, Envelope 19)
    - Naugatuck. Helicopter flying over flood (Box 17, Envelope 20)
    - Naugatuck. Connecticut Light and Power Company (Box 17, Envelope 21)
    - Naugatuck. Amoco Gas (Box 17, Envelope 22)
    - Naugatuck. Bulldozer (Box 17, Envelope 23)
    - Naugatuck. Pile of cars (Box 17, Envelope 24)
    - Naugatuck. Damage along river (Box 17, Envelope 25)
    - Naugatuck. Carmen's tailor shop (Box 17, Envelope 26)
    - Naugatuck. Damage to car dealership (Box 17, Envelope 27)
    - Naugatuck (Box 17, Envelope 28)
    - Naugatuck. Collapsed home (Box 17, Envelope 29)
    - Naugatuck (Box 17, Envelope 30)
    - Naugatuck. Turned over bus (Box 17, Envelope 31)
    - Naugatuck. Damaged steps (Box 17, Envelope 32)
    - Naugatuck (Box 17, Envelope 33)
    - Naugatuck. Police officer and man carring bags (Box 17, Envelope 34)
    - Naugatuck. Two soldiers in front of damaged buildings (Box 17, Envelope 35)
    - Naugatuck. Police officer on corner of damaged street (Box 17, Envelope 36)
    - Naugatuck. Police officer holding billy club in front of damaged building (Box 17, Envelope 37)
    - Naugatuck. Man cleaning up debris (Box 17, Envelope 38)
    - Naugatuck. Rexall Drugs (Box 17, Envelope 39)
    - Naugatuck. People viewing damage (Box 17, Envelope 40)
    - Naugatuck. Recovery (Box 17, Envelope 41)
    - Naugatuck. Men in lunch line (Box 17, Envelope 42)
    - Naugatuck. Kids holding up mans pants (Box 17, Envelope 43)
    - Naugatuck. Two soldiers in front of building (Box 17, Envelope 44)
    - Naugatuck. Two soldiers on front of SNET company truck (Box 17, Envelope 45)
    - Naugatuck. Men entering a Navy helicopter (Box 17, Envelope 46)
    - Naugatuck, U.S. Army helicopter (Box 17, Envelope 47)
    - Naugatuck. Men working at printing shop (Box 17, Envelope 48)
    - Naugatuck. Printing press operation (Box 17, Envelope 49)
    - Naugatuck. Printing press (Box 17, Envelope 50)
    - Naugatuck. Three men loading truck (Box 17, Envelope 51)
    - Naugatuck. Pile of printing materials (Box 17, Envelope 52)
    - Naugatuck. Men moving printing supplies (Box 17, Envelope 53)
    - Naugatuck. Printing building (Box 17, Envelope 54)
    - Naugatuck. Printing room (Box 17, Envelope 55)
    - Naugatuck. Large barrel (Box 17, Envelope 56)
    - Naugatuck (Box 17, Envelope 57)
    - James Brewster to Rudolph M. Hennick, gift acknowledgement letter, 1956 July 30 (Box 17, Envelope 58)
  - Barbara Lee Collection, 1955 August; T001765
    This collection shows scenes in Collinsville.
    - Car in a hole (Box 18, Envelope 1)
    - Car in hole (Box 18, Envelope 2)
    - Recovery trucks (Box 18, Envelope 3)
    - The Bridge (Box 18, Envelope 4)
    - The Bridge (Box 18, Envelope 5)
    - The Bridge (Box 18, Envelope 6)
    - The Bridge (Box 18, Envelope 7)
    - The Bridge (Box 18, Envelope 8)
    - The Bridge (Box 18, Envelope 9)
    - The Bridge (Box 18, Envelope 10)
    - Crane with house (Box 18, Envelope 11)
    - Crane with house (Box 18, Envelope 12)
    - House under water (Box 18, Envelope 13)
    - House with no front (Box 18, Envelope 14)
    - Damaged home (Box 18, Envelope 15)
    - Damaged home (Box 18, Envelope 16)
    - Damaged home (Box 18, Envelope 17)
    - Damaged home (Box 18, Envelope 18)
    - River with building (Box 18, Envelope 19)
    - River with building (Box 18, Envelope 20)
    - River with buildings (Box 18, Envelope 21)
    - River with building and bridge (Box 18, Envelope 22)
    - Water flowing into town (Box 18, Envelope 23)
    - shadow of a person taking picture (Box 18, Envelope 24)
    - Collapsed building (Box 18, Envelope 25)
    - River flowing into town (Box 18, Envelope 26)
    - River flowing into town (Box 18, Envelope 27)
    - River flowing into town (Box 18, Envelope 28)
    - Damaged town (Box 18, Envelope 29)
    - Damaged town with river (Box 18, Envelope 30)
    - Damaged town with river (Box 18, Envelope 31)
    - Collapsed building with wall (Box 18, Envelope 32)
    - Calm river (Box 18, Envelope 33)
    - Building with river (Box 18, Envelope 34)
    - Men on wall (Box 18, Envelope 35)
    - Damage on side of road (Box 18, Envelope 36)
    - Gas station with damage (Box 18, Envelope 37)
    - Collapsed house on car (Box 18, Envelope 38)
    - River with men to right (Box 18, Envelope 39)
    - Man on top a pile of wood (Box 18, Envelope 40)
    - Truck with pole (Box 18, Envelope 41)
    - Truck with pole (Box 18, Envelope 42)
    - Collapsed building (Box 18, Envelope 43)
    - Men looking over damage (Box 18, Envelope 44)
  - Prescott Bush Papers, 1955; T001862 (Box 19)
    Photocopies of photographs in the Prescott Bush papers transfered to Archives & Special Collections at The Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut in August 1991.
    Includes scenes from Ansonia, Beacon Falls, Bristol, Collinsville, Cromwell, Derby, Farmington, Hartford, Naugatuck, New Hartford, New London, New Haven, Putnam, Seymour, Simsbury, Stafford Springs, Stamford, Torrington, Washington, Waterbury, Winsted.
  - Anita Olson Flood of 1955 photo album, 2010-013; 27 scans
    This collection shows scenes in Putnam.
    The Connecticut State Library does not hold the original photo album but only digital scans of each page
  - Seymour, 1955; 2010-035; 55 photographs (2 envelopes), b&w (Box 22)
  - Ansonia, 1955; 2010-040; 26 photographs (1 envelope), b&w (Box 22)
  - Norwalk, 1955; 2012-048; 14 photographs (1 envelope), b&w (Box 22)
- Series 4. Tropical Storm Irene, 2011
  - Department of Energy and Environmental Protection (DEEP) Photographs, 2011; 2 compact discs; 2012-018
    RESTRICTED